{
    "id": "7ff033d1c78e48f4b55ad5f16f1f5ea3",
    "title": "Other, another and others: exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "a42217841a4849da95cd7ebf62f03269",
            "title": "Other, Another And Others",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Can I have …………………… piece of cake?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "another",
                        "other",
                        "others"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She has bought ………………… car.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "another",
                        "other"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Have you got any ………………….. ice creams?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "other",
                        "another",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She never thinks about ………………….. people.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "another",
                        "other"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "They love each ………………… very much.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "other",
                        "another"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Where are the ……………………… boys?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "other",
                        "another"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He never thinks of …………………",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "other",
                        "another",
                        "others"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "We will be staying for …………………… few weeks.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "another",
                        "other",
                        "others"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "They sat for hours looking into one ………………… eyes.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "other",
                        "other's",
                        "another's"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "They talk to each ………………… a lot.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "other",
                        "others",
                        "another's"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}